Chapter 1

Julie Thompson rearranged the Easter chocolates for the fourth time that morning. Something about it still didn’t suit her. Bunnies and flower cutouts lined the walls, and Sue Anne Deveraux, the store’s owner, had pronounced it charming.

But no matter how many cute pictures she put around the sweet shop, piles of snow still lined 3rd Street. Spring didn’t look like it was making any effort to show up soon.

She moved a caramel egg half an inch.

“Will you stop fussing?” Sue Anne entered from the hallway that separated the shop from her living quarters, coat in hand. “As soon as someone buys something, all your arranging will be for nothing.”

“Could be, but I need to use my art degree for something. It may as well be to make Sweets Montana look the best it can.”

“Whatever,” her friend and boss said, waving a hand and sending sparkles from her engagement ring in rainbows around the room.

“Have you set a date?” Julie wiped her hands on her apron and rearranged packages on the side shelf.

“August 22,” Sue Anne said with a smile. “I’m counting on you to be my maid of honor, you know.”

“I’ll be there. But I have some say in the dress.”

“We’ll see about that.”

“Just don’t make it southern—all bouffant with lace.”

“Please. My gown isn’t even going to be in that style. Speaking of which, we need to make an appointment at Rococo’s to look at dresses.”

“Sure.” After marrying off four sisters, Julie was used to the drill. Her wedding day was a long way off, if ever. Tony, her boyfriend, was a nice enough guy, but she didn’t feel the spark her mother had always talked about.

“Where are you going?” she asked, moving the egg back where it had been.

“Zach and I are looking at invitations. Be back in an hour or so.” The doorbell jangled noisily as she left with a sway in her step that hadn’t been there before Zach had come along.

 “I shoveled the front walk!” The door banged open a few minutes later. Redheaded Jaiden dashed in, leaving wet boot prints across the floor.

She grinned. The nine-year-old had been one of their staunchest supporters since Sweets Montana opened more than a year ago. He’d quickly made himself indispensable for outside work—shoveling, weeding, and carting around boxes as big as he was.

It didn’t hurt that he had a sweet tooth partial to chocolate.

“Cash or candy?” she asked.

“Money,” he said, his dimpled grin fading a bit. “We’re going camping this summer. I want a new fishing rod, and Mom says I have to save up half.”

Smart mother.

Julie pulled the cash from the jar, and added in a few jellybeans.

“Awesome, Julie!” He stuffed the ones in his jeans pocket and the candy in his mouth, his full grin back on his face. “Fwnk u,” he mumbled as he sped back outside, almost knocking over a man with a cane as he opened the door to the shop.

“Sorry, mister!” Jaiden dodged around the man, whose gaze followed him. A slight smile played on his lips.

When he turned back, Julie steeled her expression. What had once been an aristocratically square-jawed face was marred by a series of scars on the right side of his cheek. His light brown hair was stylish in a way that announced, “Not from here.”

His classic blue eyes pinned her to the counter.

God, she wanted to paint him. Scars and all.

She had to find out everything about him. Why did he have a cane? The scars? Where was he from? Going?

Why had he walked into Sue Anne’s shop?

Bunnies and flowers couldn’t compare to the man in front of her.

“Can I help you?” she asked.

Hopefully, the quivering mass of her insides wasn’t visible externally.

She’d never had this reaction to a man before.

• • •

Why was the store clerk staring at him? Logan Collins tensed his abs. He should be used to this by now. His scars and cane attracted attention. Usually, people were more surreptitious about it.

He bit back a snarky remark. Why should Montana be any different from New York? “Can I help you?” the woman repeated.

She looked at him expectantly, her brown shoulder-length hair framing her parted lips and dimpled chin.

She was pretty.

No matter.

Squaring his shoulders, he moved forward, cursing the cane that aged him beyond his twenty-eight years.

“My uncle, Willy ...” he began.

“Willy!” A grin spread across her face. “How is he? You must be Logan—from New York, right?”

Logan nodded.

“He talks a lot about you. Here to get some chocolate?”

He’d moved from the “not from here” to “related to someone here” category. Not entirely suspect, but a step up from the normal rural viewpoint of an out-of-stater. Had attitudes changed any since he’d been a kid? What the hell had prompted him to get on that plane?

He cleared his throat.

“Actually, he’s not doing so well,” he said. “My uncle’s in the hospital, being treated for cancer. I figured I’d pick up some chocolates to cheer him up.” He allowed himself a smile. “My uncle has a sweet tooth, but I suppose you know that.”

“I do.” Her laugh was like a thousand camera strobes going off at the same time. “In fact, he has a standing order with us. I was about to pack and ship it to Phillipsburg. How about you take it with you instead? It’ll only be a few minutes.”

As she placed chocolates in a fancy box, he scrambled for conversation topics. “How long have you lived in Missoula?”

“Only since college. I went to the university.” She looked at him and grimaced. “Even though it’s been almost two years, I haven’t managed to leave yet.”

“Why would you want to?”

“I grew up in Grass Range, out east a bit. It’s a lot more open. Sometimes it feels hemmed in here, like the mountains are too close.” She closed the box and tied a ribbon around it.

If she thought Missoula was too crowded, she’d never make it in a place like Manhattan.

“Here you go.” She handed him the box.

“What do I owe you?” He pulled out his wallet.

“Nothing,” she said, shaking her head in emphasis. “Willy’s got an account. He’s all paid up. Please tell him to get well soon.”

“Well, then.” She was a girl in a candy shop. A pretty girl, but no one he’d ever see again. And he didn’t want to. It was all coming back. The only one in the family who’d ever taken to the West was his uncle. Like his mom, he was quite happy in New York, thank you very much. “I’ll be going. Thank you.”

“Wait.” She scurried around the counter, a chocolate bunny in her hand. “Tell him this is from me ... I mean Sue Anne and me. She’s my boss.”

“A bunny?”

“Willy has quite a sense of humor,” she said with a smile that looked out of practice but hit him in the solar plexus like it was a fast return from an expert player.

“Yeah, he does.”

As she handed him the plastic-wrapped package, their hands brushed. Heat exploded in his body. He gave a slight shake of his head as he stared into her eyes.

Not here. And not now.

• • •

The air in the shop must have left when Logan did because Julie couldn’t breathe.

What had Willy said when he’d picked up his chocolates a few months ago? His nephew had been in a horrible car wreck, something about the girlfriend dying, and Logan having to give up his professional tennis career.

A pro tennis player. Who was she kidding? That spark when they’d touched had been in her imagination.

Too bad it never occurred with Tony.

Shaking off the experience, she returned to the customer orders. The new plan Sue Anne had developed seemed to be working. They already had ten subscribers, and the program was only in its second month. Willy had been their first customer.

Willy. He’d always made them laugh when he came in, often bringing fresh produce from his ranch or a local market. Willy couldn’t be old enough to have cancer. Except these days, the disease didn’t have an age limit.

What about her? She’d done nothing with her art, using Sue Anne’s business as an excuse to put her career on hold. Her paints were drying out from lack of use.

It was time for a change.

• • •

Logan pulled into the underground parking lot of the hospital, his heart rate accelerating as the all-too-familiar atmosphere chilled his bones. Ever since the accident, he’d hated being anywhere near hospitals.

He located the elevator and got off on the first floor. An older woman with a nametag smiled at him.

“Can I help you?” she asked.

Everyone in this state was so damn eager to be of use. Totally different from New York where people had the good sense to mind their own business. He’d go crazy if he stayed too long.

His uncle was staring at the television when he walked into the semiprivate room. The other bed was empty.

Willy raised a hand in greeting, a smile gathering on his lips. He looked fit; only the pallor under his permanent tan and the fatigue in his eyes gave away his illness.

“Good to see you.” His uncle’s voice was raspy. “Sorry I wasn’t home to see you when you got here. How was your trip?”

Normal, everyday conversation as if nothing was odd about having it in a cancer ward.

“How’d you know I was coming?” Logan asked.

“Instinct.”

“I brought you these. They said you had a standing order.”

“That I do.” Willy took the box, touched the outside ribbon, and put it on his nightstand. “I’ll open them later.”

“Who waited on you—Julie or Sue Anne?” Willy asked.

“Julie, I guess.”

“Pretty little thing, isn’t she? And nice. Very sweet. She’d make a good girlfriend.”

“Don’t get started with your plotting, Uncle Willy.” Logan pulled out the guest chair and sat down. Ever since he’d turned fifteen, his uncle had been throwing one girl or another at him, hoping to get him to stay and work the ranch.

“But she is pretty, isn’t she?”

“Yeah. But she lives here, Willy. Even if I can’t do the circuit on my own anymore, I’m going to coach. That means New York or on the road.” Even if the plane, rental car, and hotel life was getting old, he hadn’t figured out what else he was good at doing.

 “How long are you in here for? I mean, is it just for some more chemo, and the drive is too much? Are they doing other treatments?”

His uncle looked away for a moment before turning back.

“I’m afraid it’s a life sentence with no chance of parole.”

The air lay heavy in the room.

Shit.

“How long?” he managed to squawk out.

“Don’t know.” Uncle Willy gestured to the chocolates and forced a grin. “I’m sure these will extend my life for a few hours.” The smile broadened. “Of course I could be a here a little longer if you’d agree to stay and run the ranch with me.”

Logan groaned. He’d forgotten how much his uncle was like a one-issue radio talk show host when he got his mind on something.

What would happen to the ranch if ... when ... Willy died?

“I’ll miss you.” He touched the old man’s hand, a tightening in his throat choking any further words.

“Yeah. I’ll kinda miss me, too.” He stared at the blank wall for a moment. “I’ve left the ranch to you.”

Great. One more thing to take care of before he went home.

• • •

Logan put the Ford Escape into gear and pulled from the parking lot, his mood as dark as the day when he’d been told Deborah had died. Good thing he’d decided to fly to Montana over his mother’s protests to get away from her smothering. A day later could have been too late. Much as he’d never understood Montanans, he loved his uncle.

He pulled onto Highway 90. The roads were clear, but the sun had set, and he had a long way to go. Loud country music and coffee fueled him until he got close to the ranch, where his phone chirped.

Whoever it was needed to wait. Willy’s drive was a bastard to navigate, hidden by partially melted then refrozen snow.

Why the hell did Willy want to deal with this all winter?

He negotiated his way up the porch and through the door. Then he poured his aching muscles into the armchair, exhausted, but effervescently alive from the exercise.

He stared at the phone for several minutes before he listened to the message. Gloom settled on his shoulders.

“This is St. Patrick’s Hospital in Missoula,” the voice mail informed him. “Can you please give us a call when you get this number?”

He erased the message but didn’t immediately dial. It couldn’t be good news.

When he’d gotten on the plane, he’d anticipated long talks with his uncle around the wood stove.

He’d gotten less than fifteen minutes.

“I’m sorry,” the woman on the other end said to him when he finally dialed. “There’s no easy way to say this. Your uncle has passed.”

“Thank you for letting me know,” he said.

She told him where to pick up his uncle’s effects and asked about the funeral home.

“I don’t know. I’ll have to get back to you.”

After he punched off, his hand sank to his lap. The braided rug was barely visible until the moon came up, reflecting on the untouched snow to make the room almost as bright as day. Willy’s spirit settled into the other chair with a newspaper.

Gone.

An orb of pain throbbed in the pit of his chest, until he moved from the chair a few hours later, joints stiff from unfamiliar postures. Without turning on any lights, he shed his clothes and crawled into his childhood bed.

Chapter 2

The next morning, he ruffled through the papers in his uncle’s desk. Where would he have left instructions? The only thing that he could find was the note his uncle had left for him to find when he’d gotten there. This time he read it all the way through. At the bottom, Willy had scrawled, “If you need anything, ask Sarah.”

Who the hell was Sarah?

Maybe the girl in the chocolate shop knew. She seemed to be aware of a lot of things about Willy.

He took the card he’d found on Willy’s refrigerator from his wallet and dialed.

“Sweets Montana. How can I help you?”

The girl he’d met ... when? Only yesterday. His throat tightened.

“I’m ... I’m ...” C’mon, Collins, hold it together.

“Logan, is that you?”

What was her name? Think, damn it.

“Yes. It’s Logan. Is this Julie?”

“Your voice sounds strange. Is everything okay?”

“No ... um ... it’s not.” He couldn’t breathe.

“It’s Willy, isn’t it?” Her voice was soft.

Were his eyes tearing?

“I’m afraid so,” he said.

“I’m so sorry.”

“Can I do anything?” she asked.

“You wouldn’t happen to know a Sarah, would you?”

“Yes. That’s who Willy was seeing. He brought her in a few times. She was a really nice lady.” She gasped. “Oh. You’re going to have to tell her, aren’t you?”

“Yes.” He took in another gulp of air. “Do you happen to know where I can find her?”

“Willy said she waitressed at Does—you know, the place on the main drag in Phillipsburg?”

The place he’d gone for ice cream every weekend with Willy.

“They’re probably not open now. You might try Sunshine Station on the highway. I think they went there every weekend for breakfast. It’s Saturday, you know.”

“Guess so.”

“Oh, Logan, let me know if there’s anything else I can do to help.”

“Okay. I will. Thanks.”

He smiled after he hung up.

Sunshine Station was a combination gas station, convenience store, casino, and restaurant housed in a weathered building. If Sarah wasn’t there, maybe they’d know where to find her.

When he asked a waitress, she pointed to an older woman sitting by herself.

He hesitated for a second before taking a deep breath and crossing to the table.

“Excuse me,” he said. “I’m Logan.”

“Of course you are,” she replied. “Willy has shown me your pictures. Sit down. Get a cup of coffee. I’m finishing up my breakfast before heading out to Missoula.”

He sat, and she stared at him for a few seconds before her face folded in on itself. “He’s gone, isn’t he?”

All Logan could do was nod.

“I’m sorry. I know you two were close.” He touched her hand briefly. No doubt her grief would be delayed for privacy, and he didn’t want to intrude.

She nodded.

“Do you have any idea where his will and instructions are?” he asked after a few moments of silence.

“Probably the kitchen. That’s where he spent most of his time, so that’s where he kept everything of importance.” She gave a wan smile. “He did tell me one thing though. He wants a box of chocolates with him in the casket.” She shook her head. “Strange sense of humor, Willy had.”

Logan chuckled, relieving a little more of the strain in his chest.

“How about the funeral home he wanted to use?”

“Anaconda. It’s the closest one.”

He tried to remember where that was.

“About thirty miles southeast,” she supplied, apparently aware of his lack of understanding of area geography. “Past Georgetown Lake.” She picked up her coffee and stared into it. “You’ll let me know when the services are.”

“Sure will.” There didn’t seem to be anything else to add.

After briefly touching her shoulder, he left her to her grief.

• • •

After a week of wind and chill, midday temperatures promised to be in the sixties—unusual, but not unheard of in Montana’s fluctuating spring. Outside Julie’s window, the buds sprouted on the branches.

If she didn’t get out of this apartment, she was going to throw something—something soft and unbreakable but something. Her heart longed to break out of the mountains and head east toward Butte, but daylight had only started the stretch to its summer length. She wouldn’t have enough time to get to her destination, paint, and return home.

She’d have to settle for the Bitterroot.

Not that the scenery down the valley contained by the rounded Sapphire Mountains to the east and the jagged granite of the Bitterroots to the west was any less dramatic.

It wasn’t home, and it never would be.

But she’d insisted on the day off, so it may as well be done.

Grabbing a sketchpad, a box of pencils, and a camera, she warmed up her aged VW Beetle and headed south.

Well, warmed up as the convertible would ever be. It was a totally impractical car for Montana, but it fit her quirkiness and her budget. If she could figure out a way to get beyond minimum wage, she’d worry about a new one.

Taking the East Highway, she headed down to the wildlife refuge. There was an old barn she’d been aching to paint for years, easily visible from the dirt road that snaked through the marsh expanse. With sketches and photos, she’d be able to create her finished painting indoors. The light from the long front windows of her apartment worked well at certain times of the day coincident with the absence of her two roommates.

A studio of her own was going to be another purchase that would have to wait until she made her first million.

Not likely for an artist. Why couldn’t she be inflicted with a desire that was financially rewarding? Her father was a banker, and her parents had raised them with solid, middle-class, work-ethic values. Where had she gone wrong?

Even the chocolate shop was starting to turn a solid profit.

Maybe she’d grow up some day.

Fat chance.

Pulling to the side of the dirt-gravel road, she got out, camera in hand. The crisp air delighted her.

The sun cooperated, highlighting the white structure and emphasizing the shadows with its angles. Jagged peaks stood in crisp resolution to the cyan sky.

She stood at the edge of the snow-covered grasslands and snapped quickly, getting as many angles as she could before the light changed again.

That’s it. The perfect perspective.

She put the camera down. Her fingers flew fast over the sketchbook, capturing quick sketches of angles and shadows.

Forty-five minutes later, her exposed fingers became unmanageable, and she retreated to the car, her lungs filled with clean air.

If only she could do this every day.

She studied the sky.

Maybe a quick lunch in Stevensville before a new set of sketches and photos as the sun drifted closer to the horizon.

As she made her way to town, the iridescent red and green of a pheasant caught her eye when he scurried from the road into the dried rushes.

She was turning twenty-six this year, edging closer to thirty. Time to start making her dreams into reality.

Or she’d be forced to walk down the dreaded wedding aisle. Most of her high school friends were already on their second baby.

But how was she going to support herself while she tried to sell her artwork? How did other artists do it?

That was the problem with a degree in art. Oh, she knew how to paint, but she didn’t know the first thing about business, except what she’d learned from Sue Anne.

Julie pulled her car into a diagonal slot in front of the Stevi Cafe—basic food within her budget. She ordered a burger, fries, and iced tea, and settled down with her current read, The Birth of Venus.

 Soon she was wrapped up in the Medici and Renaissance Venice, the early rustic spring fading from her imagination. What would it have been like to live in that time with all its vibrant color and rich architecture?

“Julie?” A familiar voice brought her back to the present.

“Professor Allen.”

“Oh, please.” The young woman laughed. “You’re not in my class. Call me Diane.”

“Oh. Okay.”

“May I sit for a moment? Find out what you’re working on?”

Professor Allen—Diane—had always made her feel her work was important, gently suggesting ways to achieve the technique she was trying to master. How was Julie going to tell her she hadn’t picked up a brush in close to six months? In spite of her drying mouth, she gestured to the chair.

“I’m meeting someone, and I see you’re reading—isn’t that a wonderful book? So I’ll just be a minute,” Diane said. “What are you working on? Have you sold anything? You were such a dedicated and talented student—a joy to teach.” Diane looked at her expectantly.

“Um, I haven’t had a chance to work on anything lately. I’ve been too busy helping my girlfriend open her chocolate shop.”

“Chocolate?” The woman made perfect eyebrow arches.

“I worked in a sweet shop during the summers at home, so I know the basics.”

“Well, that’s all very noble and everything, but you shouldn’t give up your art. In fact, I’ve got a great opportunity for you. I’m opening a small gallery for local artists, particularly those who don’t exhibit other places. It’s hard to get started in the art world—I know that from experience. That’s what I’m trying to do—give others a leg up. What do you say?”

“What type of thing are you looking to show?”

“Your best work. Whether that’s pastels, watercolor, a drawing, even photos. It would be nice if it was regional—more chance of selling—but that’s less important. I’m opening in June. Think you can pull something together by then?”

“Uh ... okay ... sure ... yes.”

“Great!”

She couldn’t squander this opportunity.

• • •

The envelope was in the last place Logan looked, of course, tucked in the bottom of a knife drawer. Maybe Willy thought he’d have to defend his wishes to the death, although the darkened blades looked incapable of doing much harm.

He grabbed one of the sharp knives from the set hanging on the kitchen wall, slit the envelope open, and pulled out the note, leaving the heavy legal document where it was.

Logan,

If you’re reading this, know I had a good life and I’m at peace. You were the brightest spot in my life until Sarah came along a few years ago. She’s been a good companion, and ...

Why did people always leave out the good stuff?

Treat her well.

He heard Willy’s voice in those few words. Whenever he’d talk about his horses, he’d say the same thing: “Treat them well.”

Shit. Horses. Were there any left? Had they starved to death from his neglect?

He pulled on his coat, not quite warm enough for the temperature, and fought his way to the barn, coming close a few times to falling but always finding his balance. A core workout at its finest.

As he approached the barn door, he noticed other tracks in the snow that had fallen since he’d arrived.

Who?

He moved with greater care, on the alert for an intruder. Maybe it was someone finding shelter in the barn during the winter months. It wasn’t unheard of, but why wouldn’t Willy have left that information in the note?

The door swung inward without a problem. He ran his hand against the wall, flipped a switch, and overhanging, industrial lights glared on. No one was in the barn. There was, however, a pretty roan staring at him cautiously.

Treat them well.

The horse was another thing Willy had forgotten to mention.

“It’s okay,” he murmured as he moved closer. “I’m not here to hurt you—just want to find out if you’ve got food and a clean stall.”

The horse nickered and nodded its head.

“That’s it,” he soothed. He wished he had an apple or something equally equine approved as a peace offering for his neglect.

As Logan moved closer, the horse shied and took a step back. He stood at the gate and waited, like his uncle had taught him as a boy.

“Horses like to take things on their own terms,” Willy had said. “They’re kinda like people that way.”

Logan inspected the area around the horse, which looked to be a mare.

About a quarter of a bucket of water and a handful of oats. Stall could use a mucking.

As soon as she accepted him, he’d tend to her. It was going to be a beast given his maimed leg.

The mare stretched her neck and gave his shoulder a slight nudge with her nose.

“Oh, you’re a playful one,” Logan said and rubbed the smooth, thick hair. As soon as it warmed up, the mare would shed, but for now, she was well protected against the chill nights. A blanket was draped over the next stall. “What’s your story?”

He continued to rub the horse, reaching as far as he could to scratch her chin and neck.

The mare stepped forward and sniffed his black leather coat before snorting her disapproval.

“Too close to home.” Logan laughed. “Sorry, gal. Next time I’ll wear Uncle Willy’s Carhartt.”

A quick search told him there was no food left in the storage area—only an empty bag. The spigot and hose were where he remembered them, so he refilled the bucket with clean water.

The mare drank greedily.

Had she been alone since Willy went in the hospital? If so, why had there been any water or food at all?

He did a half-assed job cleaning out the stall, but it was better. He left the barn amid the mare’s nickered protests. He’d have to get some more food for her. Another thing on his growing list.

He reheated a cup of coffee in the microwave and sat at the kitchen table to finish reading the letter, saving the will for last.

The rest of the note let him know that Willy had always considered him a son, if not legally, then in spirit.

“You really belong out here,” the old man had said, “not locked in that competitive hot water where you spend your time. Just because you’re good at something and it’s easy for you doesn’t mean it’s right for you.”

It’s because it’s the only thing I’m good at.

A tear ran down his cheek. The note sounded exactly like the old man—opinionated and strong-willed. The final paragraph in the note made him shake his head.

The perfect woman for you is here, in Montana, not on the road somewhere. As you follow my instructions and the terms of my will, you’ll meet many. While any one of them will do, there’s one who would be the best for you to marry. No, I’m not going to tell you who it is. You’ll have to figure that out for yourself. You’re a bright boy. You’ll manage.

Your loving Uncle Willy.

Trust his uncle to manipulate him from beyond the grave.

Well, it wasn’t going to happen. After Deborah’s death, it was going to be a long time before he got close to another woman.

He opened the instructions for the funeral and burial. While it all seemed routine, one request made him smile. Sarah had been right. His uncle wanted a box of Sweets Montana chocolates put in his coffin. If they didn’t have chocolate in heaven, a situation he couldn’t imagine, he wanted to have one last shot at his favorite food.

A chance to see Julie again. His heartbeat picked up.

It was just stress. Too much going on. The horse. Funeral. Probating the will and getting rid of the ranch. The will left him some possessions, a good-sized chunk of money, and the ranch. Another sum, as well as permission to use the ranchland for riding, for Sarah.

Then there were the conditions.

He read through them four times before he put the paper on the table. He understood having to stay at the ranch for six months. Uncle Willy wanted to make sure he knew what he was doing when he sold it.

But he didn’t care. The Wildlife Federation whatever could have the damn place. He needed to get his life back together—his real life.

The other condition made no sense at all. Take a Montana girl to a Griz football game?

He’d be gone by then.

His uncle really had been intent on forcing him to fall in love with someone who was from the state.

Ridiculous.

He checked the lawyer’s name on the will—someone here in town. As Sarah had indicated, the funeral director was in Anaconda.

Montana logistics. No short distances.

Logan pulled out his phone and went to work.

The funeral director was efficient. He knew Willy and knew what he wanted. Once the hospital released the body, he would take care of everything, including transport. He let Logan know Willy had lots of friends, so he’d requested a viewing be set up and notifications sent to local papers.

They agreed to hold the service and burial in five days.

“Willy has a plot picked out in Phillipsburg, and we’ll take care of the transport there and subsequent burial. Do you want to say a few things there as well?”

What would he say? He hadn’t seen Willy in a decade. Maybe it was something Sarah would do.

He’d figure it out.

“Sure.”

As soon as the arrangements were finalized, Logan called the hospital. They told him he’d need to come in, sign some documents, and retrieve his uncle’s things.

He promised the lady on the phone he’d be in the next day.

Douglas Crowley, Esquire, was one of two lawyers in Phillipsburg. Logan looked up the phone number to make an appointment. The sooner he got the ridiculous clauses struck down, the better.

Then he’d get on the next flight out, away from old memories, his uncle’s manipulations, and Montana women.

Chapter 3

Julie sorted through tubes of paints and brushes and tossed anything that was no longer functional. While she couldn’t afford to replace everything, if she was going to create a painting worthy of her instructor, she’d need the best she could gather together. Diane’s request was a godsend. If this was good enough, where could she go from here?

Spring flirted with the day. As she drove through the university district, sunlight slipped through the budding trees and dappled the rounded hood of her VW. Weight magically lifted from her shoulders. It was a glorious day!

Not for everyone.

Had Logan found Sarah? He had a hard road ahead, making arrangements for the funeral and handling his uncle’s will. When her grandmother had died, it had taken a long time for her father to do everything required. It would be extra hard since Logan was still recovering from his accident.

Could she help him in some way?

She parked at the small lot by the university bookstore, one of the few places in town to get art supplies. Forty-five minutes later, she’d collected most of what she needed, including several practice canvases. A sandwich and soda from the Good Food Store completed her supplies, and she headed back down to the Bitterroot Valley. While there were still patches of snow in the shadows and the jagged peaks were well covered, the sun was warm enough that she could find a relatively dry place to set up to do some plein-air painting.

Her first strokes on the canvas were hesitant. She pushed forward. The only way to find out if she could still paint was to actually do it. The first colors were hopeless; the greens, yellows, and browns that seemed so natural on the fields and mountains before her turned to a muddy brown on the canvas.

She was so anxious to finish; she wasn’t taking the right preparation to get started. She didn’t have to do a perfect replica of the white barn, but to paint a suggestion of colors and shapes to use in the final piece. With the sketches she’d made and the photos she’d taken, she would be able to create the picture.

Moving away from the unsightly blot, she focused on the building, the centerpiece of the painting, counterbalanced by the tall peaks of the border. Blending and lifting color from the surface finally achieved the results she wanted—different shades of white with a rough texture. She made notes of what she’d produced and moved on to the next piece, the granite grays followed by the browns and greens of field and trees.

She lost track of time as she immersed herself in the task.

The sun had grown close to the craggy mountain summits when she packed up her stuff and put it in the car. It wasn’t much, but it was a start.

Even better, she’d seen glimmers of the flow she’d experienced when she’d first begun painting. There was hope, but to hit the deadline Diane had given her, she was going to have to concentrate on the work at hand, with no time or energy for anything—or anyone—new.

Like Logan.

But she still wanted to do something to help him. He was amid strangers—friendly strangers—but he still had to feel lonely. She’d call him from the chocolate shop tomorrow. Just a friendly call.

After all, she still had a boyfriend. The last few times Tony had called to arrange a date, she’d put him off. Maybe now was the time to break up with him. She needed to focus on her career.

Her life was rapidly changing direction.

• • •

“I’m afraid, Mr. Collins, the terms of your uncle’s will are unbreakable,” Douglas Crowley told Logan the next morning. “I drew it up myself to make sure it was ironclad.”

Nothing to do but let the wildlife people have it.

He sank farther into the chair.

“Why did he put these restrictions on the sale? I don’t live here. I don’t want to live here. And I’m not looking to get married to anyone, much less a girl from Montana.”

“He’s not asking you to marry the girl.” Douglas chuckled. “Just take her to a Griz game.”

“You don’t know my uncle. He’s got more up his sleeve than that.”

“Oh, I know Willy quite well. We’ve been playing chess together for years.”

Willy played chess?

Who cared? All he had to do was sign the papers relinquishing the ranch and head back to his life.

The lawyer straightened out in his chair and folded his hands on the desk. “It’s a beautiful time to be here. Why don’t you enjoy it for a little while? Papers will be here next month, too. You look like you could use some time to heal.”

Logan grunted. He didn’t want to get into his personal life with this stranger. What was it with this place? Everyone had an opinion on other people’s business.

“Do you know anything about the horse in Willy’s barn?”

“A horse? No.”

“I got some food for it—she looked hungry. Uncle Willy didn’t mention anything about it in his note, and it’s not in the will.”

“Nope.” Crowley shook his head. “But I guess it’s your horse from the way the will is drawn up. If you decide to turn everything over to the federation, it will then be their horse.”

Great. Another responsibility. What would a federation do with a horse?

Same thing he would do—sell it.

“Sarah might know about it,” the lawyer added.

When he stopped by Does Brothers, the lady at the counter told him Sarah had taken a few days off but gave him her number.

Should he call her now? She was still dealing with things. Although he did have to tell her the service logistics.

He took out the phone and stared at it. His mother had called, probably when he was out of range. His finger hovered over “Call back.”

The damn thing rang.

Not his mother’s number.

“Hello?”

“This is Julie. Sweets Montana Julie.”

“Yes, I remember you.” Much better than Mother. “How are you?”

“I’m fine, but how are you? I guess ... I guess I wanted to find out how you did with Sarah.”

“I told her. I think she kind of expected it.”

“Yeah.”

What else was there to say? He wanted to talk to her.

Hmmm. More than talk, he wanted to see her.

“Hey,” he said. “Willy has a strange request. Can I stop in later today?”

“Sure, I’d like that.”

“Me, too.”

A ray of sunshine broke through the gloom of Willy’s death.

As he drove to Missoula, the day remained beautiful. Blue skies and vibrant sun sparkled off the patches of snow and emerging grass. He sang along with the music, drumming his fingers on the steering wheel.

At the hospital, he signed a number of forms, confirmed the name of the funeral home, and went through Willy’s things as they were placed in a paper bag: a dog-eared mystery novel, a wallet with the usual cards, and a jeweler’s box that contained a small diamond ring.

His mood dipped. Sarah would never get her engagement ring from Willy, although Logan was sure his uncle would want her to have it.

As he waited for the elevator, he tried to think if there was anything else he needed from stores that weren’t in Phillipsburg—which was almost everything. He was sure there was something—staples if nothing else, but he had no clue what they were or even how long he’d be here.

It would take a few weeks to settle all of Willy’s affairs. Maybe he should stay a few weeks after that. He’d never been in Montana in the spring.

And he should return his mother’s call. Hell, he should have done it already.

He pulled out of the garage and headed down Orange Street, threaded his way through downtown, and continued down Higgins.

The shop was empty when he walked in, but the bell jangled cheerfully.

“Be right there!” someone sang out from the back.

His pulse quickened.

Julie emerged from the back, wiping her hands on a towel.

“Cute,” he said, pointing to the black satin apron with frilly lace. Not his usual style, but she pulled off the look.

What would she look like with only the apron on?

Heat flushed his neck. Once again, he was a teenager wanting a girl to like him.

• • •

He was back.

Her skin developed goose bumps, even though the shop was warm.

“Hello, there,” she finally said, tossing the towel she was holding on the shelf below the display cases. “I’m sorry about your uncle.”

He didn’t move.

She wanted to move closer to him, but what would happen if she stepped into his space? Instead, she smiled encouragingly. At least she hoped it was encouraging. She didn’t want to scare him off. Not this man.

“I ... um ... need a box of chocolates for a coffin.”

This was certainly a first. Willy had had a strange sense of humor.

“Did you have something in particular in mind, or do you want me to choose?” she asked. If she kept the transaction businesslike and efficient, maybe there would be air to breathe again.

“You choose. You know what he liked.”

She picked up one of the small white boxes they used for samples. What would Willy like in heaven? She was sure he was there; she’d never encountered a nicer man.

Her gaze met Logan’s over the top of the display cabinet. Why was he staring at her? It should bother her, but it didn’t.

She smiled at him. Not an innocent smile.

Their gazes broke at the tap of Sue Anne’s heels.

“Oh, hello,” Sue Anne said. “Is Julie taking care of you?” She looked from one to the other, her eyebrows narrowing slightly.

“Very well,” Logan said, more than one layer of meaning in his tone.

“Sue Anne, this is Logan, Willy’s nephew from New York.”

“How nice to meet you, Logan,” she said. “How is our favorite customer, Willy?”

“Dead,” Julie and Logan said at the same time, sharing a gallows humor grin.

“Oh, no! What happened? Did his cancer return?”

“I’m afraid so.”

The lightheartedness disappeared. Logan swallowed, his Adam’s apple rising and falling.

She wanted to kiss him and make it better.

Oops. No. She wanted to kiss him to find out what it was like. Her gaze rose to look at his lips.

Sue Anne cleared her throat, and Julie snapped her head around to find her staring at the two of them.

“Is there anything we can do to help?” Sue Anne asked. “Do you need anything?”

“Julie’s handling it,” Logan said.

“Okay, then.” Sue Anne’s voice didn’t sound like his statement reassured her. “I guess I’ll go back to making fudge.”

Please do.

As soon as she left, Julie pulled a dark-chocolate-covered truffle from the case and walked to him.

“Here. Chocolate makes everything better—at least, that’s what I’ve been told.”

“Thank you.” He slipped it from her hand, leaving behind currents of electricity, like thin strands of static.

They stood, caught in the moment, staring at each other. She lost herself in the depth of his movie-star-blue eyes. She’d never known anyone in real life to have eyes that color.

He lifted his hand as if to stroke her cheek.

Something in the kitchen clanged.

“When is the service?” she asked, scurrying back to the counter. She shouldn’t be flirting. She already had a boyfriend.

“Saturday.”

“Packing them up this early is no good. They’ll go stale.” She put the box back on the counter.

“It’s a coffin ... Julie. He’s not going to eat them. I have a freezer.”

“No. Sweets Montana chocolates do not go in a freezer.”

“What is it you expect?” Logan asked. “I can’t come back here between now and then. It’s a long drive. Things to do.”

“I’ll bring them to you closer to the service.”

“To Phillipsburg?”

“Why not?” Her breath quickened at the image of him at his uncle’s ranch. Would Logan actually wear worn clothes, or would he be still stuck in stuff that looked like he’d pulled it from department store packaging as the image of what a Montana cowboy should look like?

In spite of the cane and the scars, his physique made her pulse quicken. And there was that moment only a few minutes ago ...

Logan cleared his throat, and she dragged her gaze back to his eyes.

“Phillipsburg?” he asked, a slight tinge of red in his cheeks. “Why would you come all that way?”

“I liked Willy.” She leaned against the display case. Sue Anne would have a fit if she saw her. “In fact, I’d like to go to the service if you wouldn’t mind, and put the chocolates in myself.”

Expressions on his face changed—a tightening of the jaw and lips before switching back to a neutral look.

“Sure,” he said. “But that’s even farther—Anaconda.”

“You’re not really going to have a service in Anaconda, are you?”

“What is it with you? First chocolates for a dead man can’t go in the freezer; now I can’t have the service in the only place that has a funeral home—a funeral home Willy picked out by the way. He’s my uncle.”

They glared at each other for a few seconds before she took a deep breath.

She wasn’t being fair. The man had just lost a relative—a close one, given all of Willy’s conversation about his nephew.

“Sorry. I know this is a tough time, but it’s just ...” How could she explain distances, mountain passes, and old people in one of the country’s physically largest yet least populous states? “Have you considered doing an additional service in Phillipsburg? Willy was in his seventies or so. A lot of his friends are going to be elderly. A closer service—one that doesn’t require driving the road over the pass by Georgetown Lake—would allow them to honor their friend without putting their lives in danger.”

“Oh.”

Yes. Indeed. Oh.

She tried to tame her snark. Logan had just been through a terrible ordeal.

“What are you going to do now?” Damn. She’d put her foot in it.

“Meaning?” His lips tightened again.

“I’m probably not supposed to talk about this,” she said and pushed herself away from the display case to touch his arm.

She was crossing all kinds of barriers.

“But your uncle talked a lot about you. He was proud of you.” She let her hand stay on his arm and looked into up into his eyes. “I know you’re a professional tennis player and you were in an accident.” She tried to lighten what she was saying with a grin. “I don’t think I’ve ever seen a tennis player dashing around the court with a cane.”

She held her breath and waited for his reaction.

His lips remained tight for a few more seconds before they began a slow release to a smile. His head arched back, and he let out a rich laugh that sounded like it came from the pit of his belly.

She let go of his arm and took a step back.

“I’ve got to ... got to ...” He stumbled to one of the cafe chairs and sank into it, still doubled over with laughter.

Country music rose from the kitchen, accompanied by Sue Anne’s enthusiastic, if off-key, voice.

Logan laughed harder.

It was a better reaction than anger. Had her remark really been that funny?

Long gasps indicated the laughter was subsiding.

Now what would he do?

He finally looked up and wiped his eyes.

“I haven’t laughed that hard since ... well, since ...” His wave encompassed his leg, cane, and face. “It was wonderful. Thank you.”

Using the cane, he pulled himself to his feet and took a few steps in her direction before he held up his hands in the gesture for surrender.

“You win. You can bring the chocolates for the coffin to the funeral. That way they’ll be safely stowed before we get to the cemetery. That’s where we’ll hold the service.” He glanced to the sky. “That is, if the weather will cooperate.”

“Too early in the season to tell,” she said. “Don’t believe the weather people. They might be right for the next five minutes, but after that, it’s all guesswork.” She paused. “As far as I know, the town doesn’t really have a community center. Maybe one of the churches has a big room you could use after the burial for the service. Some of these folks won’t be able to handle the rough ground. Sarah might know.”

“What was the relationship between them? Do you know?” he asked.

“Willy liked to talk when he came here.” She shrugged. “He would sit in a corner, have a hot chocolate or chocolate soda, and talk with him for a bit if we could. He mentioned Sarah for the first time last year. I ... uh ... got the impression they were quite close.”

“Hmmm” was all he said as he took something from his pocket. “That would explain this. I found it with Willy’s things.” He handed her the box.

Inside was a modest but pretty diamond ring.

“What are you going to do with it?” She handed it back.

“I’ll give it to her. I’m just not sure when. Probably after the funeral and service sometime. Give her a chance to get her bearings.”

“How long are you staying?” Maybe they could see each other. Have lunch or something.

“I’m not sure. Montana hasn’t always been my favorite place.”

“Oh? Why is that?” She stepped closer.

“Kid stuff. You know. City boy in a country town. I had to prove myself every summer. Never did learn to shoot a rifle.”

“Don’t worry, I’ll protect you from the bad guys.” Light danced in her eyes.

“You shoot?”

She nodded.

“Amazing.” He crossed the remaining distance between them. “You are pretty different from any girl I’ve ever known.”

“City girls.” She put a tease in her voice.

“Can’t hold a match to country girls.”

The remaining air left the room as he lowered his head to kiss her.

His lips were firm and lit a fire in her. Totally different from how Tony kissed.

Tony.

She pulled back.

“I’m sorry,” he said. “I shouldn’t have done that.

Yes, you should have.

More. She wanted more.

But she’d never cheated on anyone before, and she wasn’t going to start now.

“Service at the funeral home is at ten. I’ll find out when the cemetery service will be. Give me a call on Friday.” He seemed to force a smile back on his face. “Thanks for everything—the chocolate, the sympathy”—he grinned for a second—“the laugh.”

“You’re welcome.” She returned to the area behind the counter.

“See you Saturday.” He paused at the doorway and turned to her. “You don’t happen to be a Griz fan, do you?”

“Are you kidding? I’m a graduate. What else would I be? A Bobcat fan?”

“Probably not.” He grinned again. “Then consider yourself invited to a game.”

She stared at the doorway long after the bell stopped ringing.